So on this topic of how to have discussions we've talked about some techniques.
所以关于如何进行讨论这个话题，我们已经讨论了一些技术。
Then we looked at some phrases we can use to actually start these questions.
然后我们查看了一些可以用来实际开始这些问题的短语。
And again those are not the only phrases we can use.
再说一遍，这些不是我们可以使用的唯一短语。
There are just some examples.
只是一些例子。
There are many variations.
有很多变化。
Different ways of asking these questions.
提出这些问题的不同方式。
Now let's actually look at some real examples so that we can get a feeling about how to do this.
现在让我们实际看一些真实的例子，以便我们了解如何做到这一点。
Our topic is something I care very much about.
我们的话题是我非常关心的。
Street food vendors street food being not so clean sometimes.
街头食品摊贩街头食品有时不那么干净。
But the problem is it's very delicious.
但问题是它非常好吃。
So I always want to eat it but I think maybe I can't.
所以我总是想吃它，但我想也许我不能。
It's not very clean.
它不是很干净。
So we could ask some questions if we're going to have a discussion about this.
因此，如果我们要就此进行讨论，我们可以提出一些问题。
I'm always having discussions about this with friends.
我总是和朋友讨论这个问题。
OK what do you think.
好吧，你怎么看。
What do you think could be done to ensure ensure means make sure.
你认为可以做些什么来确保确保意味着确保。
What do you think could be done to ensure that street food vendors again these are people selling food
你认为可以做些什么来确保街头食品供应商再次成为卖食品的人
on the street that street food vendors are selling clean food and following food safety rules.
在街头食品摊贩出售清洁食品并遵守食品安全规则的街道上。
What do you think could be done.
你觉得可以做什么。
Sort of like saying what could we do.
有点像是在说我们能做什么。
What could people do that basic question that I've mentioned before now we're getting somebody's idea
人们可以做什么我之前提到的这个基本问题现在我们得到了某人的想法
about how to solve this problem.
关于如何解决这个问题。
Give me some solutions.
给我一些解决方案。
Give me some ideas.
给我一些想法。
Well we could have an app or we could make sure that people have a Yelp sticker or something like that
好吧，我们可以有一个应用程序，或者我们可以确保人们有一个 Yelp 贴纸或类似的东西
with a QR code that people could scan or we need to keep street food vendors in certain areas so that
带有人们可以扫描的二维码，或者我们需要在某些区域保留街头食品摊贩，以便
the whatever blah blah blah blah blah people can give their ideas.
胡说八道的人们可以提出他们的想法。
OK let's look at another one.
好的，让我们再看一个。
What are the best local snacks and street foods in your city.
你所在城市最好的当地小吃和街头食品是什么？
OK.
好的。
So this is related to street food vendors in a very direct way just talking about your favorite things.
所以这与街头食品供应商非常直接地有关，只是谈论你最喜欢的东西。
Everybody likes to talk about their favorite things.
每个人都喜欢谈论他们最喜欢的事情。
So what are your favorite street foods if you don't have any in your city maybe you've been to a city
如果你所在的城市没有街头小吃，你最喜欢的街头食品是什么？也许你去过一个城市
and you could talk about that.
你可以谈谈。
Oh well there's a blah blah blah.
哦，好吧，有一个废话。
And in this city I could talk for an hour about this one if you were going to open a falafel stand falafel
在这个城市里，如果你要开一家沙拉三明治摊，我可以谈一个小时
is how food falafel.
沙拉三明治是怎么吃的。
Maybe maybe Middle Eastern food.
也许也许是中东食物。
I like falafel.
我喜欢沙拉三明治。
I'm not sure if there are any stands that sell just falafel.
我不确定是否有任何只卖沙拉三明治的摊位。
Maybe I just like falafel so much that I call them falafel stands even though they actually sell other
也许我只是太喜欢沙拉三明治了，我称它们为沙拉三明治摊位，即使他们实际上卖的是其他的
stuff too.
东西也。
If you were going to open up a falafel stand in New York City NYC is New York City.
如果您要在纽约市开设沙拉三明治摊位，那么纽约市就是纽约市。
That's where I live.
那是我住的地方。
So I used this example and wanted to stand out.
所以我使用了这个例子，想要脱颖而出。
That means you want people to notice you.
这意味着你希望人们注意到你。
You want people to go Oh what's that.
你想让人们去哦那是什么。
How would you market your stand.
你将如何推销你的立场​​。
Stand is your where you sell right.
展位是您正确销售的地方。
Sometimes it's called a cart.
有时它被称为购物车。
Sometimes it's called a stand sometimes in New York it's called a truck.
有时它被称为展台，有时在纽约它被称为卡车。
OK.
好的。
How would you marketed how would you promote.
你将如何营销你将如何推广。
How would you get others to know.
怎么让别人知道。
How would you advertise.
你会怎么做广告。
So you would use maybe you would talk about social media.
所以你会使用也许你会谈论社交媒体。
Talk about videos talk about how you would spend money.
谈论视频谈论您将如何花钱。
Talk about discounts and coupons.
谈论折扣和优惠券。
I don't know whatever you would do to get people to come to your falafel truck or your falafel stand.
我不知道你会做什么来让人们来你的沙拉三明治卡车或沙拉三明治摊位。
And it's just an example.
这只是一个例子。
Right.
正确的。
But it's an interesting question.
但这是一个有趣的问题。
What do you think about the idea of making food carts illegal.
您如何看待将食品车设为非法的想法。
Now someone could just say I don't like the idea bad idea.
现在有人可能会说我不喜欢这个主意坏主意。
That's a simple answer right.
这是一个简单的答案。
But then you have to say well why why do you think it's a bad idea.
但是你必须说好为什么你认为这是一个坏主意。
Then they have to explain.
然后他们必须解释。
So it's OK to answer this question in a simple way and then follow with why.
所以可以用简单的方式回答这个问题，然后再解释为什么。
So hopefully this has given you a pretty clear idea about how we can explore or talk about a main topic
所以希望这能让你对我们如何探索或谈论一个主要话题有一个非常清晰的想法
and then ideas related to it and use different ways to ask questions that are interesting about interesting
然后与它相关的想法并使用不同的方式提出有趣的问题
ideas that make the other person feel I have something to say.
让对方觉得我有话要说的想法。
This is an interesting question because you're asking me for my opinion.
这是一个有趣的问题，因为你在问我的意见。
You're asking me to explain something about my life.
你要我解释一下我的生活。
You're asking me to talk not just asking me for information.
你要我说话，而不仅仅是问我信息。
OK.
好的。
Keep that in mind.
记在脑子里。
And let's let's look at an assignment.
让我们看一个作业。
You can do to practice this.
你可以这样做练习。
So you should have now a very good idea about how to ask these questions from the last lesson.
所以你现在应该对如何从上一课中提出这些问题有了一个很好的了解。
How to start a conversation.
如何开始对话。
And now here's how to ask good questions that can make other people want to talk with you.
现在这里是如何提出可以让其他人想与您交谈的好问题。
So I'd like you to practice it.
所以我想让你练习一下。
What I'd like you to do is look at this topic famous people who have dropped out of college that means
我想让你做的是看看这个话题 大学辍学的名人 这意味着
they've quit college or they quit college for example Mark Zuckerberg Steve Jobs and Bill Gates all
他们已经退出大学或者他们退出了大学，例如马克扎克伯格史蒂夫乔布斯和比尔盖茨所有人
of these three very famous people left university.
这三个非常有名的人离开了大学。
They QUIT.
他们退出了。
They come up with three interesting questions around this topic using some of the phrases that we learned
他们使用我们学到的一些短语围绕这个主题提出了三个有趣的问题
in this lesson and then to test it.
在本课中，然后对其进行测试。
I would like you to ask yourself the questions and answer the questions give the answer to the question
我希望你问自己问题并回答问题给出问题的答案
and record yourself doing that.
并记录自己这样做。
Or have the discussion with a friend ask a friend the questions.
或者与朋友讨论，向朋友提问。
If they go.
如果他们去。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Or if they say Oh yeah.
或者如果他们说哦，是的。
The answer is blah blah blah.
答案是胡说八道。
And then it feels like it's hard to move the conversation forward and keep going.
然后感觉很难推进对话并继续进行。
Probably a problem with your questions.
可能你的问题有问题。
So to do this well remember your goal is to get the other person's brain to turn move get the juices
所以要做好这件事，记住你的目标是让对方的大脑转动起来，得到果汁
flowing we say get the juices flowing.
流动我们说让果汁流动。
All right.
好的。
Good luck.
祝你好运。